excellentguide.com 2009-03-23

# Excellentguide Privacy Policy

Excellent Guide Web directory understands and respects your concerns about privacy. At the same time, we do ask that you provide information about yourself in order for us to understand your needs better and make your experience at Excellent Guide more valuable to you. 

We created this Privacy Policy to provide you with notice of what information Excellent Guide may collect and how such information may be used or shared with third parties, and how such information relates to the operation of the Site. This privacy policy is subject to change at anything, and you are responsible for checking periodically to view new updates to the privacy policy.  
  
  |     
**What Information Do We Collect?**  
  |     
  
Excellent Guide Web directory does not secretly collect information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information during the site submission process. This information may be used to contact you if there is a need for a revision to your site reviews. Excellent Guide Web directory notes and saves information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, and IP address with each query. That information is used to verify our records and to provide more relevant services to users.  
  
  |     
**Links to Other Sites**  
  |     
  
The sites displayed as search results or linked to by Excellent Guide Web directory searches are developed by people over whom Excellent Guide Web directory has no control. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. It is important that you preview their Privacy Policy and remove any cookies from your computer if you have any concerns.  
  
  |     
If you still have questions feel free to contact us.  
  |     
Excellent Guide Web directory  
P.O Box 637  Hayneville, Alabama 36040  
webmaster(@)excellentguide.com
